Muhammad Ilyas Muharizki

 $+62\ 882\ -\ 1890\ -\ 6249\ |\ \underline{muhammad.ilyas72.mi@gmail.com\ |\ https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadilyas72/}{https://github.com/muhammadilyas72}$

Bandung, Jawa Barat, 40191

I am a final year mathematics major student with a profound interest in Data Engineering. I have experience learning data engineering through data academy which is spread across data warehouse, ETL, ELT, and database. I also studied SQL which is needed for data processing. I am able to work well as a team and I am committed to complete my work, even though there are challenges in it.

Academic Experience

1. Independent Study Data Academy - South Jakarta, DKI Jakarta August 2023 - Desember 2023

Data Engineering Academy

- Learn the concepts of data engineering and data warehouse.
- Learn SQL for data engineering.
- Designing ETL jobs using Talend.
- Cloud computing for data engineering.
- Learn data visualization for data engineering.
- Train soft skills.
- Final project: Analisis Distribusi Cuaca dan Pengaruhnya terhadap Hasil Panen di Jawa Barat

2. Independent Study Zenius - South Jakarta, DKI Jakarta February 2023 - July 2023

Data Analytics

- Learn the basics of data science, python, data analysis, and data visualization.
- Learn exploratory data analysis and statistics for data science.
- Learn databases using SQL queries.
- Create a dashboard using looker studio.
- Final project: Home Credit Default Risk Analysis and Prediction Using Supervised Learning Algorithm

Project

1. Home Credit Default Risk Analysis and Prediction Using Supervised Learning Algorithm

- a. Group project
- The goal of this project is to classify customers based on the customer's ability to make payments on time and to make predictions to see customer capabilities based on factors that influence them
- c. Developed using pandas
- d. Dashboard developed using looker studio
- e. The source of dataset from kaggle.com

2. ETL using Talend

- a. Individual project
- b. Perform design and Job Development Talend
- c. Perform data transformation with Talend
- d. Perform error handling and debugging

- e. Learn advanced techniques in Talend
- f. Integrating Talend with system External

Education

1. Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia - Bandung, West Java September 2020 - Present

Bachelor's Degree Program in Mathematics, GPA: 3.60/4.00

Organization

1. BEM Himatika Identika UPI 2021

Staff Divisi Kerohanian